themefoxx.com 2018-02-11

# Privacy Policy | ThemeFoxx

The privacy policy describes the kinds of information we may gather during your visit to these Sites, how we use your information when we might disclose your personally identifiable information, and how you can manage your information.

 **By visiting our site, you are accepting the practices described in our privacy policy, including our use of cookies and similar online tools. If you do not agree to the terms of this privacy policy, please do not use this site.**

We reserve the right to modify or amend the terms of our privacy policy from time to time without notice. Your continued use of our Sites following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. If we intend to apply the modifications or amendments to this privacy policy retroactively or to personally identifiable information already in our possession, we will provide you with notice of the modifications or amendments and seek your consent to such use.

#### What Information Is Collected?

We collect two basic types of information from you in conjunction with your use of the Sites: non-personally identifiable information and personally identifiable information. Non-personally identifiable information does not individually identify you, but it may include tracking and usage information about your general location, demographics, use of the Sites and the Internet. Personally identifiable information is any information that can individually identify you and includes, your name, address, phone number, and email address, or non-personally identifiable information that has been linked to such personally identifiable information.

####  **Personally Identifiable Information**

As a general matter, you can browse the Sites without submitting your personally identifiable information to us. However, there are a number of circumstances in which you may supply us with your personally identifiable information, including when you subscribe to our publications, newsletters, and other content; place an order; register for a Site or any part thereof; complete a poll or participate in market research; enter a contest; upload content; or when you seek employment at ThemeFoxx.

####  **Non-Personally Identifiable Information**

When you interact with the Sites, we may collect certain information that does not identify you individually (“non-personally identifiable information” or “non-PII”), such as demographic data; information about your computer, mobile device, or other device that you use to access the Sites, including IP address, general location information, unique device identifiers, browser type, browser language, and other transactional information.

We may also collect information about your use of the Sites, including your search terms and search results, and additional “traffic data” such as time of access, date of access, software crash reports, session identification number, access times, and referring website addresses. Our servers may automatically keep an activity log of your use of our Sites. In addition to non-identifiable individual information, we may collect aggregate data regarding the use of the Sites.

####  **Collection of Your Source IP Address/Location Information**

We collect and store your device’s source IP address which may disclose the general location of your device at the time you access the Sites. Advertisements and certain content may be directed to you as a result of this data.

####  **How Do We Use Your Information?**

We use the information we learn from you to help us personalize and continually improve your experience on the Sites, including to:

  * Provide you with the content, products, and services you request
  * Post your user generated content to our Sites as you request
  * Communicate with you about your account or transactions with us and send you information about features and enhancements on or to our Sites
  * Communicate with you about changes to our policies
  * Communicate with you about your comment to a story or topic
  * Personalize content and experiences on our Sites, including providing you recommendations based on your preferences
  * Provide you with advertising including advertising based on your activity on our Sites or activity on third party sites and applications
  * Administer our loyalty programs
  * Administer contests, giveaways, promotions, and polls
  * Optimize or improve our products, services and operations
  * Detect, investigate, and prevent activities that may violate our policies or be illegal
  * Perform statistical, demographic, and marketing analyses of users of the Sites and their purchasing patterns

#### Who Can See Your Information?

We will not disclose your personally identifiable information collected from the Sites to any organizations not part of ThemeFoxx or its subsidiaries or related entities, except as described in this privacy policy.

####  **Links to Third Party Sites**

Our Digital Properties may contain links to other websites operated by third parties we do not control and this Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected through our Digital Properties. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these other websites.

#### How Do the Sites Use Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies?

Like many websites, we use cookies, web beacons and similar technologies to record your preferences, track the use of our Websites and your exposure to our online advertisements. We may also use these technologies to monitor traffic, improve the Sites and make it easier and/or relevant for your use.

Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but, if you prefer, you can usually modify your browser setting to disable or reject cookies. If you delete your cookies or if you set your web browser to decline cookies, some features of the Sites may not work or may not work as designed.

We also use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”), on our Websites. Google Analytics uses cookies or other tracking technologies to help us analyze how users interact with and use the Websites, compile reports on the Websites’ activity, and provide other services related to Websites activity and usage.

The technologies used by Google may collect information such as your IP address, time of visit, whether you are a return visitor, and any referring website. The Websites do not use Google Analytics to gather information that personally identifies you.

The information generated by Google Analytics will be transmitted to and stored by Google and will be subject to Google’s privacy policies.

We may partner with third party advertising companies to better provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. These third party advertisers may use cookies alone or in conjunction with web beacons or other tracking technologies to collect information about you when you use the Sites. They may collect information about your online activities over time and across different websites and other online services. They may use this information to provide you with interest-based advertising or other targeted content.

These online advertising partners do not have access to or use your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number or other personally identifiable information from us, without your consent. They may, however, use persistent identifiers to anonymously track your Internet usage across other websites in their networks beyond these Sites. While we restrict their further use of such information, such third parties may, with sufficient data from other sources, be able to personally identify you, unknown to us.

Third-party ad serving companies and other unaffiliated advertisers also display advertisements on our site. As part of their service, they may place a separate cookie on your computer or utilize other data collection and tracking technologies, to collect information such as your IP address, browser type, the server your computer is logged onto, the area code and zip code associated with your server, and whether you responded to a particular advertisement. We do not control these third parties’ tracking technologies, how they may be used, or the information they may collect and we are not responsible for the privacy policies or the content of those third parties. Please visit the sites of those businesses at the links above to review their privacy policies. We may add or change the list of third party ad servers from time to time and we encourage you to check this section for changes.  **You can learn more about about online advertising at  **[ **www.aboutads.info/consumers**](http://www.aboutads.info/consumers) **.**
